Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ericamarske (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Leadership

Management

Nursing

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Registered Nurse

BLS Provider

EFSET 73 Proficient (CEFR C2)

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support Experienced Provider (ACLS)

Honors-Awards

Sigma Theta Tau Member

Erica Marske, BSN, CCRN

Registered Nurse

Cleveland/Akron, Ohio Area

Summary

Critical care nurse with two years of experience on an 18-bed medical intensive care unit. I am skilled in cardiopulmonary resuscitation (CPR) and advanced cardiovascular life support (ACLS), Electronic Health Record (EHR) Systems, and primary and secondary research methods. I have recently become involved in unit quality improvement measures through work as a Geriatric Resource Nurse, Vascular Access Resource Nurse, and preceptor.

Experience

Cleveland Clinic
Critical Care Registered Nurse
August 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months)
Cleveland. Ohio

- •Developed skills working with an interdisciplinary team to deliver patientcentered care. Assess, diagnose, plan, implement, and evaluate interventions with the team.
- •Order and interpret diagnostic tests to evaluate patient status.
- •Work on quality improvement teams as a Geriatric Resource Nurse and Vascular Access Resource Nurse.
- •Skilled in preventing hospital-acquired infections through use of central line protocol, urinary catheter protocol, and ventilator-association pneumonia prevention interventions.
- Assist with determining end-of-life care goals
- Adept at prioritizing interventions and time management

Valparaiso University

1 year 10 months

Civic Reflection Facilitator
October 2017 - May 2018 (8 months)

Valparaiso, Indiana

Supplemental Instruction Leader August 2016 - May 2018 (1 year 10 months) Valparaiso, Indiana

Tutored students in first-level collegiate anatomy and physiology. Attended the students' class, prepared informative review materials, led weekly sessions, offered study advice, and facilitated a collaborative learning environment.

Ancilla Systems
Development Team Assistant
May 2017 - May 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Hobart, Indiana

Specific duties included grant searching, grant preparation, and writing. Coordinated small programs and events for five major non-profit ministries in the northwest Indiana area. Generated proposals for specific projects in need of funding and analyze best sources of funding through Foundation Center Online.

Skills: Constant Contact, Microsoft Word.

Loyola Medicine
Patient Observer
October 2015 - December 2016 (1 year 3 months)
Maywood, Illinois

Assisted high fall risk patients with ADLs on the following units: medicalsurgical, burn, pediatric, emergency department, and oncology. Specific skills included: restraint documentation, vitals Q1-4h, therapeutic communication skills.

Group Mission Trips
Project Leader
May 2015 - August 2015 (4 months)

Coordinating relational service projects within a community over the course of seven weeks. Responsibilities include managing volunteer work throughout each week and maintaining relationships with non-profit partner organizations.

Education

Valparaiso University
Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2014 - 2018)